Guide to the Tamiment Library Newspapers PERIODICALS.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- S
  - South Sound Alliance, The Place of publication: Portland, Or. Publisher: Oregon Coalition of Alternative Human Services, 1986-1989 (Box 8)
  - Southern California Teamster Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: Joint Council of Teamsters, No. 42, 1990 (Box 413)
  - Southern Patriot Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Southern Conference Education Fund, 1959-1976 (Box 395)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7001 and Film R-7060)
  - Southern School News Place of publication: Nashville, Tenn. Publisher: Southern Education Reporting Service, 1955-1956 (Box 399)
  - Southern Struggle Place of publication: Nashville, Tenn. Publisher: Southern Conference Educational Fund, 1977-1979 (Box 395)
  - Space City News Place of publication: Houston, Tex., 1970-1972 (Box 395)
  - Spark Place of publication: Amherst, Mass., nd (Box 395)
  - Spark Place of publication: Baltimore, Md. Publisher: Spark, 2002-2003 (Box 395)
  - Spark Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: South Asia Students Association, UC-Berkeley, 1972 (Box 31)
  - Spark Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Party for Workers Power, 1974-2000 (Box 395-398)
  - Spartacist Britain Place of publication: London, England Publisher: Central Committee Spartacist League, 1978 (Box 399)
  - Special Bulletin Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Socialist Party (Max Delson), 1935 (Box 399)
  - Special Issue Place of publication: Vt. Publisher: Vermont Alternative Media Project (VAMP), 1979 (Box 399)
  - Special Weapon Place of publication: Albuquerque, N.M. Publisher: Special Weapon, nd (Box 164)
  - Spectre Place of publication: Ann Arbor, Mich. Publisher: Revolutionary Lesbians, 1971-1972 (Box 399)
  - Spheric Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: City College of New York, 1995-1996 (Box 111)
  - Spokane Natural Place of publication: Spokane, Wash., 1970 (Box 399)
  - Spotlight Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, 1953-1959 (Box 399)
  - Spring Movement Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Washington, Spring, 1971 (Box 399)
  - SSEU News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Social Service Employee Union Local 371, 1965-1982 (Box 457)
  - SSEU-371 Committee for New Leadership Campaigner Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: SSEU-371 Committee for New Leadership, 1973 (Box 399)
  - The Staff Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif., 1971-1973 (Box 400-401)
  - Stand By! Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Local of AFTRA, 1984-1987 (Box 402)
  - Stand Up Place of publication: Eugene, Or., 1974-1981 (Box 402)
  - Standard Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Henry George, 1890 (Box 513)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7712)
  - State and Mind Place of publication: W. Somerville, Mass. Publisher: RT, Inc., 1976 (Box 402)
  - State Bulletin / Issued by New York State Committee of Communist Party Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York State Committee of Communist Party, 1951 (Box 402)
  - State Employee News Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: New York State Employees Council 50, 1968 (Box 402)
  - Steel Worker Place of publication: Baltimore, Md., 1977 (Box 402)
  - Steel Worker Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Communist Party (US) Chicago, 1948-1950 (Box 402)
  - Steelabor: The Voice of the United Steelworkers of America Place of publication: Pittsburgh, Pa. Publisher: United Steelworkers of America, 1980-1984 (Box 402)
  - Steering Wheel Place of publication: Aurora, Ohio Publisher: Steering Wheel Corp/, 1973 (Box 413)
  - The Storeworker: Publication of the United Storeworkers, RWDSU, AFL-CIO Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Storeworkers, 1969-1986 (Box 403A)
  - The Straight News Place of publication: Anchorage, Alaska, 1971 (Box 403)
  - Straight Track: Intercraft Association of Minnesota News Place of publication: Minneapolis, Minn. Publisher: Intercraft Association of Minnesota News, 1985-1989 (Box 403)
  - Strategic Hamlet Place of publication: Isla Vista, Calif., 1970-1971 (Box 403)
  - Street Journal Place of publication: San Diego, Calif., 1969? (Box 403A)
  - Street Kids Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Street Kids, 1983 (Box 411)
  - Street Paper Place of publication: Salt Lake City UT, 1971 (Box 403)
  - Strike! Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Northeastern Federation of Anarchist-Communists, 2004 (Box 403)
  - Strike! Place of publication: Toronto, Canada, 1983-1985 (Box 403)
  - Strike Back Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Bell Workers Action Committee, Local 1101, 1971-1974 (Box 403)
  - Struggle Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: Black Liberation Newspaper, 1968-1975 (Box 403-403A)
  - Student Action Place of publication: San Bernadino, Calif. Publisher: Campus Crusade for Christ, 1972 (Box 206)
  - The Student Insurgent Place of publication: Eugene, Or. Publisher: Editorial Collective, 1990-1995 (Box 403)
  - The Student Mobilizer Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: National Student Coalition Against Racism, 1975 (Box 403)
  - The Student Mobilizer Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Student Mobilization Committee, 1967-1972 (Box 403)
  - Substance Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Substitutes United for Better Schools, 1976-1988 (Box 404)
  - Sun Dance Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Running Dog, 1972 (Box 403)
  - Sun/Dance Place of publication: Ann Arbor, Mich. Publisher: White Panther Party, 1970-1971 (Box 403)
  - Sunburst / North American Libertarian Alliance Place of publication: Tucson, Ariz. Publisher: North American Libertarian Alliance, 1971 (Box 28)
  - Sunfighter Place of publication: Wash. Publisher: Awareness Project of Monroe Prison, 1973 (Box 342)
  - Sunrise Place of publication: Macomb, Ill. Publisher: Tucker, St. John Irwin, nd (Box 403A)
  - Supporters of Silkwood Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Supporters of Silkwood, 1979 (Box 402)
  - Survival Summer News Place of publication: Philadelphia/San Francisc, Penn./Calif. Publisher: Mobilization for Survival, 1980 (Box 111)
  - Sweet Fire Place of publication: Albany, N.Y., 1972 (Box 403A)
  - Synapse Place of publication: Traverse City, Mich. Publisher: Neahtawanta Research adn Education Center, 1972 (Box 402)
- T
  - The Tailor Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: Journeyman Tailor's Union of America, 1905-1935 (Box 414)
  - Task Force Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Task Force, 1968-1969 (Box 164)
  - Tax Strike News Place of publication: Porterville, Calif., 1973-1974 (Box 414)
  - Tax Talk Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: War Tax Resistance, 1970-1975 (Box 417)
  - Taxi Drivers Voice Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Taxi Drivers Union Local 3036, 1967-1997 (Box 416)
  - Taxi News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Arthur T. Gore, 1967-1977 (Box 415)
  - Taxi News Transport Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Fred Swartz, 1963-1967 (Box 415)
  - Taxi Teamster Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Taxi Drivers Local 826, Teamsters Union Affiliated with the New York Joint Council 16, 1953-1958 (Box 415)
  - Taxi Times Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: New York Taxi Drivers Alliance, 1964 (Box 416)
  - Taxi Union News Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Democratic Union Organizing Committee Local 777, 1966-1968 (Box 416)
  - Teacher Action Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Teachers Action Caucus of the United Federation of Teachers, 1977-1982 (Box 414)
  - Teacher News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Teachers Union, 1941 (Box 289)
  - Teamsters 102 News Place of publication: Newark, N.J. Publisher: International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Local 102, 1964-1968 (Box 416)
  - Teamsters for Teamsters Place of publication: Flushing, N.Y. Publisher: Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 1981 (Box 413)
  - Teamsters Rank and File Speaks Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Detroit Metro TDU, 1982-1983 (Box 413)
  - The Technician Place of publication: Rockville, Md. Publisher: Association of Civilian Technicians, 1981-1983 (Box 415)
  - The Telephone Flash Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: United Telephone Publications, Inc., 1946 (Box 415)
  - Telephone Organizer / Telephone Workers Organizing Committee (C.I.O.) Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Telephone Workers Organizing Committee (C.I.O.), 1948 (Box 115C)
  - Telephone Workers' Outlook Place of publication: Charleston, W. Va. Publisher: West Virginia Union of Telephone Workers, TWOC-CIO, 1948 (Box 115C)
  - Tempo Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Joint Board; Fur, Leather, and Machine Workers Union, A.M.C.&B.W. of N.A. (AFL-CIO), 1969-1982 (Box 424)
  - Tempo Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Local 1-FLM, United Food & Commercial Workers International Union, 1982-1985 (Box 488)
  - Tenant Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Metropolitan Council on Housing, 1971-current (Box 424-425A)
  - Tenants United Place of publication: Bronx, N.Y. Publisher: West Bronx Tenants Union, nd (Box 414)
  - Testing Digest Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Project to De-mystify the Established Standardized Tests, 1979 (Box 429)
  - Textile Challenger Place of publication: Lawrence, N.Y. Publisher: United Textile Workers of America, 1978-1994 (Box 427-428)
  - Third Avenue Transit Victory Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: TWU-Local 100, 1944 (Box 412)
  - Third World Place of publication: Washington, D.C. (Box 38)
  - Thistle Place of publication: Cambridge, Mass. Publisher: MIT Alternative News Collective, 1990 (Box 426)
  - Through the Looking Glass Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa., 1971 (Box 477)
  - Through the Looking Glass Place of publication: Seattle, Wash. Publisher: Through the Looking Glass, 1982-1987 (Box 499)
  - Tie Lines Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: MIchigan Bell, 1976 (Box 115C)
  - Tierra y Libertad Place of publication: Mexico Publisher: Tierra y Libertad, 1962-1982 (Box 28)
  - Tiger Paper Place of publication: U.S.A., 1972 (Box 429)
  - The Times Now Place of publication: Coconut Grove, Fla. Publisher: Now Associates INC., 1970-1971 (Box 426)
  - The Times of America Place of publication: Miami, Fla. Publisher: Times of America Pub. Co., 1991 (Box 426)
  - Tin Drum Place of publication: Middletown, Conn. Publisher: Wesleyan University, 1968-1969 (Box 426)
  - Tinig-Manggagawa Place of publication: U.S.A., 1928 (Box 488)
  - TIU News / Telecommunications International Union Place of publication: Hamden, Conn.. Publisher: Telecommunications International Union, 1985 (Box 414)
  - Tobacco Worker / Tobacco Workers International Union Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Tobacco Workers International Union, 1977-1978 (Box 429)
  - Today Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Philadelphia Newspapers, Inc., 1972 (Box 414)
  - Toiler: Official Organ of the Communist Labor Party of Ohio Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Publisher: Communist Labor Party of Ohio, 1920-1922 (Box 414)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7083 and Film R-7472)
  - Torch: Newspaper of the Revolutionary Socialist League Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Revolutionary Socialist League, 1973-1989 (Box 429-431)
  - Townsend National Weekly Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Prosperity Pub. Co., 1948-1960 (Box 405-410)
  - Trade Union Action & Democracy Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: National Coordinating Committee for Trade Union Action and Democracy, 1970? (Box 414)
  - Trade Union Courier Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 2001-2003 (Box 431)
  - Trainman News Place of publication: Ind. Publisher: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1948-1958 (Box 431)
  - Transformations Place of publication: New York, N.Y., nd (Box 432)
  - Transport Bulletin (Albany-Troy Special) Place of publication: Albany, N.Y. Publisher: Transport Workers Union, 1938 (Box 412)
  - Transport Bulletin (Boston Edition) Place of publication: Boston, Mass. Publisher: TWU-Local 182 CIO, 1940 (Box 412)
  - Transport Bulletin (National Edition) Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Transport Workers Union of America, 1935-1942 (Box 411)
  - Transport Bulletin (New York Edition) Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Transport Workers' Union, 1937-1942 (Box 413)
  - Transport Bulletin (New York Weekly) Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Transport Workers Union, 1940-1941 (Box 413)
  - Transport Bulletin (Philadelphia Edition) Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: TWU, 1937 (Box 412)
  - Transport Bulletin (Taxi Edition) Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Taxi Division Transport Workers Union, 1937-1949 (Box 413)
  - Transport Voice: Official Organ of Transport Workers Union, Local 100, CIO Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: TWU Local 100, 1947-1948 (Box 413)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7063)
  - Transport Workers Link to the World Place of publication: Kempston, Bedford, England Publisher: International Transport Workers' Federation, 1941 (Box 413)
  - Transport Workers Organizer Place of publication: Los Angeles, Calif. Publisher: TWU-Local 156, CIO, 1937 (Box 413)
  - Travisty Place of publication: Suisun City, Calif. Publisher: G.I.s at Travis Airforce Base, nd-1973 (Box 164)
  - Trenton Rank & File Place of publication: Trenton, N.J., 1972 (Box 357)
  - Tribuna popular Place of publication: Caracas, Venezuela Publisher: G. Machado, 1993 (Box 414)
  - The Tribune Place of publication: Vancouver/Toronto, Canada Publisher: Pacific Tribune Publishing Association/Canadian Tribune Publishing Association, 1992-1993 (Box 434)
  - Tribune socialiste Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Parti socialiste unifié, 1960-1980 (Box 433)
  - Triple Jeopardy Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Third World Women's Alliance, 1971-1975 (Box 433)
  - Tri-State Miner Place of publication: Picher, Okla. Publisher: International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1949 (Box 433)
  - Truth Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: Trotskyist Organization, USA, 1974-1985 (Box 437)
  - Truth Place of publication: Oak Park, Ill. Publisher: Trotskyist Organization in the U.S., 1974-1985 (Box 437)
  - Turn It Around! Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Philadelphia Workers' Organizing Committee, 1971 (Box 357)
  - Turning the Tide Place of publication: Culver City, Calif. Publisher: Anti-Racist Action Publishers, 2001-2007 (Box 357A)
  - TWU Express Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Transport Workers Union of America, 1977-2005 (Box 418-422)
  - TWU Local 234 C.I.O. Transport News Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: TWU, 1955-1972 (Box 412-413)
  - Työmies eteenpäin Place of publication: Superior, Wis. Publisher: Työmies Society, 1979 (Box 412)
- U
  - U.T.O. News: Official Journal [of the] United Telephone Organizations Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Telephone Organizations, 1949-1958 (Box 458)
  - UConn Free Press Place of publication: Storrs, Conn., 1969 (Box 463)
  - UE News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America United, 1970-1991 (Box 439-442)
  - UFT Bulletin Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Federation of Teachers, 1990-1991 (Box 285D)
  - UIU Journal Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1978-1985 (Box 444)
  - UKCS News Place of publication: Nairobi, Kenya Publisher: Union of the Kenya Civil Servants, 1975 (Box 444)
  - The Ukrainian-American Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Slavic-American Pub. Co., 1977-1993 (Box 446-447)
  - Umanità nova Place of publication: Rome, Italy Publisher: FAI, 1966-1986 (Box 448-451)
  - Umsebenzi (South African Communist Party) Place of publication: Johannesburg, South Africa Publisher: Inkululeko Media and Marketing Co-operative, 2004 (Box 452)
  - Unconvention Place of publication: Philadelphia, Pa. Publisher: Independent Media Center of Philadelphia, 2002 (Box 452)
  - Undercurrent News Place of publication: Buffalo, N.Y. Publisher: Draft Resisters, 1971 (Box 452)
  - Undo News Place of publication: Princeton, N.J. Publisher: Union for National Draft Opposition, 1970 (Box 452)
  - Unemployed Teacher Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Unemployed Teachers Association, 1933 (Box 452)
  - Unidad Latina Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: El Comite, 1971-1973 (Box 452)
  - The Union Digest Place of publication: Louisville, Ky. Publisher: Tobacco Workers International Union, Local 185, 1940 (Box 452)
  - Union Label and Service Trades Department News Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Union Label and Service Trades Department of the State of New York, 1946-1954 (Box 452)
  - The Union Leader Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Chicago Journal of Street, Railway, Rapid Transit, and Bus Workers, 1942-1943 (Box 452)
  - Union Mail Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: New York Metro Area Postal Union, 1959-1999 (Box 453-455)
  - Union News Place of publication: West Palm Beach, Fla. Publisher: Local 3181, Communications Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1981 (Box 115C)
  - Union Reporter Place of publication: Pennsauken, N.J. Publisher: Union Reporter Association, 1973-1986 (Box 456)
  - Union Tabloid Place of publication: Washington, D.C. Publisher: Graphic Arts International Union, 1983 (Box 456)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7073)
  - Union W.A.G.E. Place of publication: Berkeley, Calif. Publisher: Union Women's Alliance to Gain Equality, 1974-1977 (Box 452)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7553)
  - The Unionist Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Social Services Employees Union Local 371, District Council 37, AFSCME, 1969-current (Box 457-457A)
  - Unite! Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Communist Party USA, 1975-1982 (Box 458)
  - Unite Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Marxist-Leninist Organizing Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 463)
  - United Front News Place of publication: Cairo, Ill. Publisher: United Front of Cairo, 1971-1972 (Box 458)
  - United Irishman Place of publication: Dublin, Ireland Publisher: Republican Movement, 1971-1973 (Box 458)
  - United Labor Action Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Center for United Labor Action, 1974-1990 (Box 458)
  - United National Caucus Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: United National Caucus, UAW, 1970-1973 (Box 458)
  - United Rubber Worker Place of publication: Detroit, Mich. Publisher: United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America, AFL-CIO, 1972-1988 (Box 445-446)
  - United States of ACORN: USA / ACORN Place of publication: New Orleans, La. Publisher: Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now, 1978-1983 (Box 463)
  - United Teacher Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Federation of Teachers, Local 2, 1960-1971 (Box 282-282E)
  - United Teacher (New York City Edition) Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: United Federation of Teachers, Local 2, 1972 (Box 283)
  - The United Worker Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: United Industrial Workers, Service, Transportation, Professional & Government of North America, 1983-1988 (Box 458)
  - Unity Publisher: Revolutionary Workers Movement, nd (Box 237-238)
  - Unity Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Getting Together Publications, 1978-1992 (Box 459-462)
  - Unity and Struggle Place of publication: Newark, N.J. Publisher: Revolutionary Communist League, 1972-1979 (Box 463)
  - Unity News Local 259 Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: UAW of America, Local 259, 1973-2002 (Box 463)
  - Unsere Zeit: UZ; sozialistische Wochenzeitung; Zeitung der DKP Place of publication: Essen, Germany Publisher: CommPress-Verl., 2007 (Box 446)
  - Up Against the Bulkhead Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: Up Against the Bulkhead, 1970-1974 (Box 165)
  - Up Against the Wall Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Columbia University Students for a Democratic Society, 1968 (Box 178)
  - Up Against the Wall Street Journal Place of publication: Ann Arbor, Mich. Publisher: University of Michigan, 1971 (Box 463)
  - Up from the Bottom Place of publication: San Diego, Calif. Publisher: San Diego Area Servicemen, 1971-1974 (Box 165)
  - UPS News Service Place of publication: New York, N.Y., 1972 (Box 248)
  - Upstream Place of publication: Ottawa, Canada Publisher: Feminist Publications of Ottawa, 1976-1979 (Box 456)
  - UPSurge Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio, 1975-1980 (Box 501)
  - UR New York Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: Entelechy Press Corp., 1969-1975 (Box 444)
  - Urban Underground Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: MDS Collective, 1970 (Box 463)
  - US China Friendship Newsletter Place of publication: San Francisco, Calif. Publisher: U.S. China Friendship Association, 1971 (Box 458)
  - Utility News Place of publication: Brooklyn, N.Y. Publisher: Transport Workers Union Utility Division, 1946-1957 (Box 412)
  - Utility Reporter Place of publication: Walnut Creek, Calif. Publisher: Local Union 1245, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1989-1992 (Box 463)
  - The UTOG News Caster Place of publication: U.S.A. Publisher: The United Taxi Owners Guild, 1964 (Box 463)
  - UTU News Place of publication: Cleveland, Ohio Publisher: United Transport Union, 1993-2002 (Box 423)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7356)
- V
  - Valley War Bulletin Place of publication: Florence, Mass. Publisher: American Friends Service Committee, 2004 (Box 465)
  - Vanguard Place of publication: Coburg, Australia Publisher: Challenge Press, 1967-1968 (Box 464)
  - Vanguard Place of publication: Fullerton Publisher: SDS, 1970 (Box 248)
  - Vanguardia obrera Place of publication: Havana, Cuba Publisher: Central de Trabajadores de Cuba, 1966 (Box 464)
  - Vermelho e Branco Place of publication: Rio de Janiero, Brazil Publisher: Instituto de Estudos da Religião, 1991 (Box 464)
  - Vermont Commons Place of publication: Waitsfield, Vt. Publisher: Vermont Commons, 2006-2009 (Box 465)
  - Vermont Freeman Place of publication: Huntington, Vt. Publisher: Hanksville Associates, 1969-1974 (Box 464-464A)
  - Verse Gazette Place of publication: New York, N.Y. Publisher: P. Werner, 1973 (Box 467A)
  - Veteran / Vietnam Veterans Against the War/Winter Soldier Organization Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: VVAW/WSO, 1975-1989 (Box 465)
  - Le Veteran socialiste Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Groupe Nationale des Aciens du Parti Socialiste, SFIO, 1963 (Box 465)
  - Veterans Stars & Stripes for Peace Place of publication: Chicago, Ill. Publisher: Veterans for Peace, 1967-1971 (Box 165)
  - Via Pacis Place of publication: Des Moines, Iowa Publisher: Des Moines Catholic Worker Community, 1981 (Box 465)
  - Vicksburg Citizens' Appeal Place of publication: Vicksburg, Miss. Publisher: Vicksburg Citizen's Appeal, 1964 (Box 465)
    Researchers must use microfilm (Film R-7480)
  - Vietnam Place of publication: Paris, France Publisher: Comite Vietnam National, 1968 (Box 465)
  - Vietnam Courier Place of publication: Hanoi, Vietnam, 1966-1971 (Box 465)